

0739308707 / 0671026987 https://nhlanhlamuthwa.netlify.app nhlanhlainnocentmuthwa@gmail.com.

Location: Durban

# Objective

Dedicated professional seeking IT jobs.

# Skills

C#, Java, MVC, JavaScript, HTML,CSS, Web API, WPF, Win Forms, Angularjs, SharePoint Design, SQL, Photoshop, Microsoft office, Microsoft Visio, UML, IT Technical Support.

# **Drivers License** Drivers License: Code 10

### Referencies

Company: SITA Name: Ncami Ngcobo Tel: +27333952481 Phone: +27832637949 Email: Ncami.Ngcobo@sita.co.za

Company: KMC Name: Mathabo Matjiu Tel: +27114045004 Phone: +27726533744 Email: mathabom@khabane.co.za

# Nhlanhla Muthwa

# Full Stack Software Developer

#### **About Me**

I believe my training, experience, and proven ability as a Technical Support Trainee and Software Developer will allow me to significantly contribute to the productivity and quality of any company's IT division.

I am a technical minded Software Developer and I have acquired valuable experience in all facets of troubleshooting, installations, and maintenance for various desktop operations, hardware, and software. I possess a unique talent for translating highly complex technical information into terms and concepts that the end users can readily grasp.

Furthermore, I am multi-task oriented, enjoy a challenge, and continually stay abreast of the latest advancements in the IT field.

# **Experience**

1 April 2018 – 31 1 May 2019 -August 2018 June 2020 Khabane State Information Majestic **Technology** Consulting Agency Working as a Working as Software Developer, **Technical Support** Developing Trainee, Assisting computer with Technical systems/programs Support duties in the Wide Area Network. using Java as core language with Agile Router Configurations, and Approach Development Generating Network Reports for utilization etc. LAN and Desktop support in

### **Education**

2013

Esizibeni High School

Matric Certificate

2017-2018

**CTU Training Solutions** 

Information Technology: Systems Development(Programming)

Departments.

2019-2020

**Net Campus** 

Information Technology: Technical Support(A+ core 1-2 and N+)